- 얘들아
- 어서 와
Listen....
저기, 내가 재닌이랑
잘될 수 있을까?
You think I have a chance with Janine?
전에도 얘기 했었잖아
We've been through this.
Don't do this to yourself.
맞아, 그럼 안 되지
그런 일은 없을 거라고
잘라 말했다면서
She made it clear it isn't
going to happen.
All right, then. I guess I shouldn't
get too excited...
그래, 알았다
흥분하면 안 되겠네
키스 한 번 했다고!
that I just kissed her!
-Are you serious?
-That's great!
- 정말?
- 잘됐다!
Yeah, well, we'll see.
두고 보자고
You kissed her?
키스를 했어?
정말 아찔한 카스였어
We kissed it up real nice.
So you ended up with Janine.
결국 재닌이랑 엮였구나
Well, congratulations,
you won fair and square.
축하한다
확실한 너의 승리야
그래, 한동안은
치열한 각축을 벌였지
Yeah, it was real neck and neck
there for awhile.
키스한 후엔 어떻게 됐는데?
So you kissed. Then what happened?
너희들한테 얘기하러 왔잖아
I came over here to tell you guys.
So she's waiting over
there for you?
재닌은 저기 내버려두고?
Yeah.
그래...
The One With The Apothecary Table
-I gotta go.
-Okay.
- 가봐야 돼
- 알았어
이러다 댄스 수업에 늦겠어
I'm gonna be late
for dance class.
Okay.
알았어
- 진짜 갈 거야
- 알았어, 그래
-Okay, now I'm really leaving.
-All right.
But can you just...
근데 입술만 남겨놓고
가면 안 될까?
just leave your lips?
- 안녕
- 잘 가요
Have you kissed her yet?
재닌이랑 키스해봤냐?
엄청나
It's awesome!
I could do it forever.
평생 할 수도 있겠어
You know what? She kisses better
than my mom cooks.
우리 엄마 요리보다
재닌의 키스가 나아
- 요리라고 말해서 다행이다
- 그래
I'm so glad you said, "cooks."
Look, it's like
imagine your best kiss ever.
이런 거야, 너희들 생애
최고의 키스를 상상해봐
이제 거기다
정확히 10을 곱해
Right? Okay, now multiply that
by, like, 10.
Wait a second, you dated Ross.
잠깐, 넌 로스랑 사귀었지?
And you date Chandler.
Okay, multiply it by, like, 50.
그리고 넌 챈들러, 좋아
50 정도는 곱해야겠다
레이첼, 우체국에
이전 신고해야겠다
Rachel, you've got to tell
the post office that you've moved.
우편물이 다 이쪽으로 와
We still get your bills and stuff.
Pottery Barn!
You can throw the rest away.
어머, '포터리 반'에서 왔다
나머지는 버려
I'm not your garbage man.
난 청소부 아냐
우체부지
I'm your mailman.
Monica, look.
모니카, 이것 봐
나 이 테이블 주문했다
Here is that table that I ordered.
-You got it from Pottery Barn?
-Yeah. It's an apothecary table.
포터리 반에서 샀어?
그래, 약종상 테이블이야
약종상이 뭔 지나 아니?
Does anyone even know what
an apothecary is?
A pharmacist.
약제사잖아
깽깽깽깽
"A pharmacist."
레이첼, 피비는
포터리 반을 싫어해
Phoebe hates Pottery Barn.
나도 포터리 반 싫어
I hate Pottery Barn too.
They kicked me out just
because I sat on a bed.
침대에 좀 앉았다고 쫓아내잖아
You took off your pants and
got under the sheets.
바지를 벗고 시트 밑으로
들어가니까 그렇지
I was tired.
좀 피곤했어
Phoebe hates Pottery Barn?
피비가 포터리 반을 싫어해?
대량생산제품은 다 싫어해
She hates mass-produced stuff.
She thinks her furniture should
have a story behind it.
가구에는 사연이
담겨있어야 한대
This has a story behind it.
여기도 사연이 있어
화이트 플레인스에서
여기까지 실려왔잖아
They had to ship it all the way
from the White Plains store.
세상에 하나밖에 없어야 돼
It's got to be one-of-a-kind.
Like that God-awful ceramic fruit
bowl she has on her counter?
혹시 걔 찬장에 있는
흉측한 과일접시 봤니?
Hey! I made that for her.
야, 내가 만들어준 거다
-You made pottery?
-Yeah.
- 네가 도자기도 빚었냐?
- 그럼
I made it out of a fruit bowl
I found in the garbage.
쓰레기통에서 찾아낸
과일접시로 만들었어
그거 집에 들여놓으면
꽤나 시달릴 거다
If you put that in her apartment,
you'll never hear the end of it.
알았어, 골동품이라고 하지 뭐
어디서 난 건지 알 필요 없잖아
I'll tell her that it's an antique.
She doesn't have to know
where it came from.
이 서랍 좀 봐
I love these little drawers.
Oh, look! It says that
it holds 300 CDs.
CD가 300장이나 들어간대
역시 고리짝 테이블이로세
Just like the apothecary tables
of yore.
고리짝이라니?
Your what?
-What?
- 어?
- 뭐?
카탈로그나 보세요
Enjoy the catalog, sweetheart.
그래서 농부 왈
So the farmer says:
"That's not a cow,
and you're not milking."
'그건 암소가 아니고
이것도 우유가 아냐'
I'm so glad you're together.
같이 어울리니까 너무 좋다
We wanted a couple to go out with,
and now we have one.
우린 늘 다른 커플이랑
놀러 다니고 싶었거든요
We're a couple of couples.
쌍쌍이 또 쌍쌍이네?
오늘 정말 즐거웠어요
레스토랑도 근사하고
I had so much fun tonight.
What a great restaurant!
챈들러, 너 자꾸
계산하고 그럼 못써
And, Chandler, I can't believe
I let you pay for this one.
고맙다, 짜샤
Thanks again, man.
If you come over tomorrow,
I'll make pasta.
내일 우리 집에 와요
파스타 만들어줄게요
그거 좋죠
-That'd be great!
-Okay.
그래도 최소한 우리가
와인 정도는 가져갈게
But at least let us
bring the wine.
- 안 그래도 돼
- 아냐, 가져갈 거야
-You don't have to.
-I insist.
-You'll get the wine, right?
-Yeah.
- 와인 준비해라
- 알았어
- 그럼 잘 자
- 그래, 내일 봐
-Okay, good night.
-See you tomorrow.
- 내일이에요
- 꼭 갈게요
Can't wait.
How are we going to get
out of that one?
어떻게 빠져나가면 좋지?
뭐?
I can't handle two
nights in a row with them.
이틀 연속 저 사람들하고
함께 지내긴 싫어
모니카랑 챈들러가 어때서?
What's wrong with them?
몰라, 그냥...
떠버리야
They're just a little...
blah!
Blah?
떠버리?
Well, you know, he's blah.
She's just...
챈들러도 말이 많고
모니카는 몸집도 작은데
목소리는 기차화통이야
She's very loud for such
a small person.
쟤들은 내 친구인데
They're my best friends.
Are you saying we can't go out?
Because that'd be a problem.
같이 못 어울리겠다면
문제가 좀 되지
아니, 어울릴 순 있지만
Of course we can still
hang out with them.
Just not two nights in a row.
이틀 연속은 곤란해
-Okay?
-I guess.
그렇지?
알았어
고마워
Thank you.
I'll sell my friends and use
the money to buy you presents.
자기가 원한다면 친구를
팔아서라도 선물 사줄게
- 나 왔어
- 그래
테이블 근사하다
What a great table!
Where did you get it?
어디서 났어?
Guess.
맞혀봐
벼룩시장?
A flea market?
거봐, 역시 단번에 찍었어
I knew you would get it
on the first guess.
Isn't it cool?
It's an apothecary table.
괜찮지?
약제용 테이블이야
You can just imagine
that this is where...
생각해봐
옛날에 약사들이 재료를
여기 담아뒀을 거 아냐
they kept all their stuff
to make potions.
이거 봐
아편 냄새도 난다
You can almost smell the opium.
Almost.
그렇구나
얼마나 줬어?
How much was it?
500달러밖에 안 해
Just only 500 bucks.
벼룩시장에서 500달러?
Five hundred bucks at a flea market?
이 물건이 새 거였을 때
가격을 묻는 줄 알았지
I thought you meant how much was it...
when it was new, back then.
아주 옛날에
It was at a flea market,
so it was like a dollar.
벼룩시장에선
한 장 정도 가나?
-A dollar?
-And 50?
1달러?
하고도 50
그러니까 한 장에다 50달러
So it was like
one and 50 dollars.
가격도 옛날 식으로 매겼구나
-They gave you the old-time pricing.
-Yeah.
- 그럼
- 좋지
Well, what period is it from?
어느 시대 거야?
고리짝 물건이야
고리짝 시절 알지?
It's from yore.
Like the "days of yore," you know?
그럼, 알고 말고
Yes, I do.
-It's just perfect.
-Oh, good.
세상에, 너무 멋지다
분명 굉장한 사연이 있을 거야
들은 얘기 없어? 원산지라든가...
I bet it has a great story too.
Did they tell you
where it's from or...?
그 얘긴 들었지
화이트 플레인스에서 왔대
Yes, that I know.
This is from White Plains.
White Plains.
화이트 플레인스...
마법의 나라일 거야
It sounds like such a magical place.
- 안녕, 나야
- 어서 와
-I'm here.
-Hi!
엄마야
Oh, my God!
- 마음에 들어?
- 내가 못살아
-You like it?
-Oh, my God!
새로 산 약제용 테이블이야
It's my new apothecary table!
로스, 피비가 곧 올 텐데
절대로 보여주면 안 돼
Phoebe will be here any second.
She can't see this.
왜? 걔도 좋아할 거야
가짜 아냐
Why not? She'll love it.
It's the real thing.
I got it at Pottery Barn.
포터리 반에서 샀거든
I know. I bought the same one.
그렇겠지, 나도 이거 샀어
And if she sees your table,
she'll know I lied.
거짓말한 거 들키게 생겼다
-I said ours was an original.
-Why?
내 건 골동품이라고 했거든
왜 그랬는데?
피비는 포터리 반을 싫어한대
Because she hates Pottery Barn.
She hates Pottery Barn?
포터리 반을 싫어해?
She says it's all mass-produced...
그러게, 공산품을 쓰다 보면
다들 똑같은 물건만 갖게 된대
nothing is authentic, and everyone
winds up having the same stuff.
So come on!
Can we cover this up, please?
금방 올 텐데
뭐라도 덮어두자
싫어, 피비한테
감추고 싶지 않아
I am not gonna hide it from Phoebe.
Although I did get some great
Pottery Barn sheets.
참, 포터리 반에서 산
테이블보가 있구나
맞아, 테이블보도 만들지?
I forgot they made sheets!
아무렴
I still can't believe
she hates Pottery Barn.
어떻게 포터리 반을
싫어할 수가 있냐?
로스, 진정해라
널 싫어하는 게 아냐
It's not like she hates you.
그래도 포터리 반인데
Yeah, but Pottery Barn?
아무래도 걔 좀 이상해
You know what I think?
She's just weird.
쌍둥이라서 그럴 거야
원래 쌍둥이는 별나잖아
It's because she's a twin.
Twins are weird.
별난 게 아니라 하나밖에 없는
물건을 좋아하는 거야
She's not weird. She likes
her stuff to be one-of-a-kind.
You know what's not one-of-a-kind?
A twin!
절대 하나가 될 수 없는 게
바로 쌍둥이지
- 안녕
- 어서 와
피비 왔으니까
이제 불 끄고 영화 보자
Let's turn out the lights
and watch the movie.
좋아
어머, 테이블보 멋지다
-Hey, cool sheet!
-You like it?
마음에 들어?
어디서 샀는지 알려줘?
-You want to know where I got it?
-Sure.
그래
벼룩시장에서 샀대
At a flea market.
You buy your sheets
at a flea market?
테이블보를 벼룩시장에서 사?
Come on, you gotta loosen the
purse strings a little.
너 노랑이짓 좀 작작해라
- 안녕
- 그래
Dinner will be ready in 20 minutes.
20분이면 저녁준비 끝나
정말 기대된다
Here is the wine to bring
over tonight.
오늘 네가 가져올
와인 여기 있어
You were also gonna
buy Monica flowers...
모니카한테 꽃 못 주는 건
어제 저녁 샀으니까 참는다
but you couldn't, because
you paid for dinner last night.
Thanks. But it's just
gonna be me tonight.
고마워, 근데
오늘은 나 혼자야
재닌은?
-What happened to Janine?
-She's really sick.
몸이 많이 안 좋아
저런
-That's too bad.
-Yeah, she's been in there all day.
그래, 종일 누워있었어
열나고, 코도 이상하고
High fever, nose problem.
It's...
phlegm, phlegm,
phlegm, phlegm, phlegm.
가래, 가래, 가래, 가래, 가래
Monica! Chandler!
모니카, 챈들러
정말 미안하게 됐어요
I'm sorry about tonight. I don't
know if Joey told you...
조이가 말했는지 모르겠는데
이 연극은 꼭 봐야하거든요
but I couldn't get out
of going to this play.
Have a great time, huh?
재미있게 놀아, 안녕
That's funny, I saw no phlegm.
가래는 전혀 안 보이는데?
Oh, no, she really is sick.
아니, 진짜로 아파
Then why is she going to a play?
근데 무슨 연극을 봐?
거 있잖아, 열을 식히고
감기를 낫게 하는 연극
Well, you know, "Starve a fever...
go to a play for a cold."
Why is Janine not coming
over for dinner?
조이, 왜 재닌이 안 오는 거야?
She didn't want to hang out with
you guys two nights in a row.
그게...
너희랑 이틀이나 연속으로
놀 순 없대, 정말 미안하다
I'm so sorry.
Why doesn't she want
to hang out with us?
왜 우리랑 놀기 싫대?
그러니까 재닌 말로는
너희가 떠버리래
Because she thinks that
you are blah.
그리고 모니카 넌
너무 시끄럽대
And that you, Monica,
are too loud.
뭐!
What?!
What?
뭐?
So she just pretended to
have a good time?
그럼 간밤엔 우리 앞에서
즐거운 척 연기를 한 거야?
She was lying to our faces?
기가 막혀서
I can't believe this.
Who is she to judge us?
뒤통수를 쳐도 유분수지
그렇게 잘해줬는데
-We couldn't have been nicer to her.
-And I am not blah. I am a hoot!
그리고 난 떠버리가
아니라 비아냥쟁이야
Come on, please, you guys.
Don't be mad.
나도 알아, 제발 화내지 마
I'm sure she said it...
그런 말을 한 건
너희가 내 친구라서
긴장했기 때문일 거야
because she was nervous because
you're my best friends.
어제가 첫 데이트였거든
And it was our first date.
Plus, she's really sick.
게다가 진짜로 아파
You said you made that up!
말도 안 되는 거
계속 우길래?
그래도 연극보다는
감기가 그럴 듯하잖아
But isn't the sick thing
better than the play thing?
둘 다 좋다, 난 모니카가
취했다는 핑계를 대는데
They're both good. I generally just
go with, "Monica's drunk again."
얘들아, 부탁이야
한 번만 더 기회를 줘
Come on, please just
give her another chance.
금방 친해질 거야
-She'll come around, I promise.
-Of course we will.
알았어
- 저녁이나 준비하자
- 그래
-Come on, we gotta make dinner.
-Okay.
그 여자 밥맛이야
I do not like that woman!
다 들려
I can hear you!
내가 시끄럽긴 시끄럽네
I am loud!
피비, 발 올리지 마
그건 새로 산...
Can you please not put your
feet up on my new..?
Old sheet.
헌 테이블보야
알았어
Oh, sure.
내 약제용 테이블!
My apothecary table!
- 뭐?
- 안 돼!
-What?
-No!
이런...
-Where did you get this?
-At Pottery Barn, okay?
이거 어디서 샀니?
포터리 반에서 샀다! 됐냐?
세상에
Oh, my God!
피비, 포터리 반에서
우리 골동품 디자인을 훔쳤어
Pottery Barn has ripped off
the design of our antique!
맙소사, 디자인을 훔칠 정도면
한 장에다 50달러는 훨 넘겠다
If they've ripped off our table...
ours must be worth much more
than one and 50 dollars.
This doesn't even
smell like opium.
이건 아편 냄새도 안 나잖아
당연히 네가 쏟은
와인 냄새가 나겠지
It smells like wine,
which you spilled.
And thanks for wrecking my sheet.
테이블보까지 해먹었구나
진정해라, 80센트 줄게
Ross, calm down. I'll give
you the 80 cents.
Okay, one more time.
한 번 더 해봐
Would you like some orange juice?
챈들러, 오렌지주스 더 줄까?
완벽한 데시벨이야
-Perfect decibel.
-I know!
나도 알아!
얘들아
그래
What are you guys doing?
뭐하고 있었어?
Nothing. We're just talking.
You know, blah-blah-blah.
그냥 얘기 중이야
알잖아, 떠벌떠벌떠벌
잘 지내보겠다고 했잖아
Come on, you said you were gonna try.
우리 재닌이랑 같이 영화나
한 편 보러 가는 게 어떨까
I came over to invite you to
a movie with me and Janine.
-What do you say?
-I'd like to...
그러고는 싶지만
(시간이 있나 모르겠네)
but I'm not sure if
we have the time.
퍽이나 웃기다
내가 어떡하면 좋겠냐
Very funny. I don't know
what to do.
서로 으르렁거릴 필요 없잖아
I really want you to get along.
함께 영화 보러 가자
신세 갚는 셈치고
Please come to the movie with us.
You owe me.
- 신세를 갚아?
- 그럼
-We owe you?
-That's right.
너희 두 사람 시작할 때
내가 도와준 거 잊었냐?
I helped you out in the
start of your relationship.
6개월이나 쉬쉬했잖아
I helped you sneak around
for six months.
I looked like an idiot.
난 핫바지 되고
갖은 수모를 다 당했어
겨우 200달러 받고
And I was humiliated.
And I only made $200.
우린 돈 준 적 없어
We didn't give you any money.
You don't think I know that?
내가 그것도 모를까
이건 어디 옆이 좋을까?
새 버드나무 의자, 사하라 책상
I can't decide if it goes
better by the new chair...
the Sahara desk...
아니면 파커 콘솔 테이블
or the Parker console table.
아예 포터리 반을 옮겨놨네
I didn't know there was
a Pottery Barn up here.
나도 알아, 내가 좀 과했지
-I know, I went a little crazy.
-A little?
좀 과해? 이 집은 완전히
카탈로그 72페이지잖아
Your place looks like page 72
of the catalog.
이것도 있네?
Look at that!
The ornamental birdcage!
Large.
관상용 새장, 대짜
- 왔구나
- 그래
로스, 조심해
그거 굉장히 오래됐어
Oh, Ross? Be careful.
That is very old.
식민지시대 새 장사들이
시장에 갈 때 썼던 거래
Colonial bird merchants used to
bring their birds to market in that.
절묘하구만
Fascinating.
또 근사한 걸 찾았구나
Another amazing find!
여기에도 멋진 사연이 있겠지?
-I bet this has a great story too.
-It does.
그럼, 식민지시대 때
방을 나누던 칸막이래
It is a room-separating apparatus
from Colonial times.
식민지시대 물건이 참 많군
A lot of this stuff is from
the Colonial times.
다른 시대 건 없니, 레이첼?
What are some other
time periods, Rachel?
Well, there's yore.
고리짝 시대 것도 있고
And, you know, yesteryear.
뭐, 지난 시대 것도 있지
레이첼은 안목이 상당히 높아
Rachel has such a
good eye for this stuff.
로스, 넌 아무래도 집을
다시 꾸며야겠던데
Ross, if you ever decide
to redecorate...
and I think you should...
레이첼한테 도와달라고 해
you should ask Rachel to help.
혼자서도 잘할 거야
He doesn't need my help.
아냐, 그런 건 치워야지
너도 그랬잖아
I think he's ready to get rid
of the.. What'd you call it?
싸구려 복제품에
공룡 쓰레기라고
The "cheap knockoffs
and dinosaur junk"?
Really?
그래?
네가 그렇게 보는 눈이
높다니 하는 말인데
You know, since you have such a
great sense of what I need..
여기 60달러 줄 테니까 피비랑
그 식민지시대 벼룩시장에 가서
Here's 60 bucks.
Why don't you take Phoebe down
to that Colonial flea market...
몇 개 사다 줘
and get me some stuff.
I don't think Phoebe wants to come.
피비는 가고 싶지 않을 거야
아냐, 가고 싶어
-I do want to.
-She does want to.
- 가고 싶다네
- 가고 싶겠지
-She does want to.
-Yeah!
그럼
-I'm gonna get my purse.
-Okay.
- 지갑 가져올게
- 그래
나중에 이거 버리면
내가 가져도 될까?
Hey, can I have all this stuff
when she makes you throw it out?
Well, sure, and I'll show you
right where you can put it.
그래, 어디다 놓을지는
내가 가르쳐주지
좋아
정말 할말이 없다
저번엔 쓸만한 게 많았는데
I guess the flea market was
just better last time.
- 로스 테이블보는 샀잖아
- 그래
Well, at least I got these
sheets for Ross.
Look at this. Pottery Barn.
이걸 봐, 포터리 반
보지 마, 눈 버린다
You know what? Don't look at it.
보지 말라니까
-Seriously, don't look at it.
-Look!
저거 봐
우리 커피테이블도 훔쳤어
There's the table
they stole from us.
정말 나쁜 놈들이네
빨랑 가자
Oh, those bastards! Let's go.
봐
저 부채도 우리 거고
새장도 비슷하고...
That fan kind of looks like ours
and the birdcage and...
잠깐, 우리 거실이랑 똑같잖아
Wait a second, this is our
exact living room!
No, it's not.
아냐, 그럴 리가 있나
자세히 보면 많이 달라
Come on, ours is totally different.
그리고 우리는...
I mean, we don't have the..
We don't have that lamp.
저 램프 없잖아
저 칸막이도...
And that screen is on
the other side.
반대로 놓여있고
세상에
Oh, my God. This is where you
got all our stuff.
너 여기서 다 샀구나
포터리 반, 맙소사
Pottery Barn! Oh, my God!
그래, 실은 여기서 샀어
정말 미안해
Okay, I did, all right?
I'm sorry.
갖고는 싶은데
네가 여길 싫어하니까...
I wanted this stuff, and I know
how you feel about Pottery Barn.
제발 화내지 마
-Come on, don't be mad.
-No, but I am mad.
아냐, 화 많이 났어
용서받을 수 없는 물건들이
모두 내 거실에 들어앉았어
Because this stuff is what's
wrong with the world...
and it's in my living room...
속상해 죽겠는데
왜 저 램프는 없는 거야!
and all I can think about is
how I don't have that lamp!
그럼 저 램프 사면되잖아
로스한테 받은 60달러로
Well, then, honey, buy the lamp.
We have that 60 bucks from Ross.
안 돼, 그럴 순 없어
I can't! I can't!
하지만...
Unless...
내가 램프를 안 사면
우리 집에서 나갈 거지?
Are you saying you'd move out
if I didn't buy that lamp?
아냐, 내가 왜 나가
No, I'm not gonna move out!
내가 램프를 안 사면
우리 집에서 나간다고?
But are you saying that you would
move out if I didn't buy that lamp?
맞아, 꼭 나갈 거야
-Yes! I would so move out.
-Then I don't have a choice.
그럼 어쩔 수 없지
램프를 사야겠네
-I have to buy that lamp!
-That's right.
물론이지
그래도 약제용
테이블은 진짜잖아
But at least the apothecary
table's real.
오늘 정말 재미있더라
다들 괜찮았지?
This was great.
Didn't everybody have a great time?
나도 좋았어, 정말이야
I did. I really did,
and I've got to say...
그리고 지난번 일은
내가 사과할게요
I'm sorry if I was weird after
the last time we went out.
그러는 게 아닌데
좀 긴장했었나봐요
I guess I was just nervous.
충분히 이해합니다
-That's understandable.
-Don't worry about it.
네, 걱정 말아요
So we can go out again?
- 그럼 또 어울리는 거죠?
- 그럼요
물론이죠
-Absolutely.
-Well, good.
- 좋아요
- 그래, 잘 자라
잘 자요
거봐
See?
재미있잖아
Wasn't that fun?
제발 이사 가자
We have got to move.
What?
그럴 줄 알았어
I knew it!
댁은 조용한 줄 아슈, 색시?
You're not so quiet yourself, missy!
내가 떠버리라고?
I'm blah? The only thing more
boring than modern dance...
모던댄스보다 더 따분한 게
있다면 그건 당신 수다야
is you talking about it.
'오, 챈들러
움직임이 너무 황홀해요'
"Oh, Chandler, I just lost
myself in the movement."
두 사람이 무슨 얘길 했겠지만
You know, I know you're talking...
떠벌떠벌떠벌로만 들리네요
but all I hear is,
"Blah-blah-blah-blah-blah."
좋아, 너 밖에서 나 좀 보자
All right, you and me!
Let's go right now!
됐어, 그만해
All right, enough!
그만하라니까
Enough! You two, go home.
I gotta talk to Janine.
너희는 집에 가 있어
재닌이랑 얘기 좀 하게
붙었으면 자기가 이겼어
I really think you could take her.
복도에서 걸리기만 해봐
You better hope I don't
see you in the hallway!
저기...
All right.
이렇게 나오면 안 되지
Look, we got a little bit
of a problem here.
내 친구들을 그런 식으로
대하면 곤란하잖아
You can't my treat
my friends that way.
- 시작한 건 저쪽이야
- 알아, 나도 그 얘긴 할게
-They said stuff to me too.
-I know, I'll talk to them about it.
내겐 소중한 애들이야
가족이나 다름없다고
They mean so much to me.
They're like my family, you know?
계속 이렇게 나오겠다면...
If you guys are gonna be
fighting all the time....
우린 헤어질 수밖에 없어
I don't think we can be together.
It just can't work, okay?
보나마나 결말이 뻔하잖아
It can't.
나 기분 엄청 상했어
I'm very upset.
그래, 알았어
Okay.
가서 사과하면 될까?
Would it help if I apologized?
그래, 그럼 좋지
더 바랄 게 뭐 있어
Yeah.
That'd be very helpful.
복도에서 걸리면 죽는 댔지?
What did I tell you about the hall?
내 잘못을 사과하러
가는 길이에요
I was coming over to
apologize for my behavior.
좋은 친구가 됐으면 해요
I'd really like it if we
could be friends.
그럼 친구인 조이
얼굴을 봐서라도
Well, I know that would
make Joey happy, so...
그렇게 하죠 뭐
I would like that too.
잘됐네요
-Great.
-Now, come on.
이리 와요
- 다행이네요
- 그러게요
-I'm glad we worked it out.
-Me too.
-I'll see you.
-Bye.
- 또 봐요
- 안녕
안 봐도 다 들리지만
-Or I'll hear you.
-That's it, big girl!
이게 진짜, 덤벼!
Wait!
잠깐!
걸리기만 해!
You'd better run!
너도 들었어?
Did you hear that?
그래
어떡하지?
-What am I gonna do?
-I'm sorry, man.
내 맘도 쓰리다
-Want to go watch?
-Yeah!
- 구경 갈래?
- 좋지
아무래도 재닌은 벅차지
You know, I'm not sure
you could have taken Janine.
제까짓 게 뭐라고
I could have taken her.
너보다 한참 큰데?
-She's much bigger than you.
-Are you kidding me?
오빠 지금 장난해?
I know what to do with tall girls.
You go for their knees.
꺽다리 다루는 방법이 있어
무릎을 까는 거야
- 어서 와라
- 여기들 있었냐?
-How you doing?
-So did she move out?
그래서 재닌은 나갔어?
그렇게 됐네
Pretty much.
너도 의외로 독한 구석이 있다
I can't believe you just
broke up with her.
서로 안 맞으면 어쩔 수 없지
When it's not right, you know it.
괜찮냐?
-You okay?
-I'll be all right.
그래, 견딜 만해
내가 기운 나게 해줄까?
-You know what would cheer you up?
-What?
어떻게?
나 내일 저녁에
침식이론 강의하거든
I'm giving this lecture on
erosion theories tomorrow night.
I think you should come.
너도 와라
You're right, that did cheer me up.
맞아, 진짜 기운 난다